{
    "id": "2191913dd29246fe9ebc8210e7086360",
    "title": "Subject Verb Agreement",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Either he or I ……………. mistaken.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "am",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Either the boy or his parents ……………… erred.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents and I ………………. lived here for five years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The council …………….. elected its President.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A number of boys ………………… caught cheating on the exam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A number of interesting suggestions ……………….. been made.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The news ……………….. true.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Each of the boys …………….. given a prize.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The chief, as well as his men, ......................... massacred.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "John, as well as James, ......................... praise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "deserve",
                "deserves"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}